Hey, hey, everybody
嘿，嘿，大家注意
We've got something to say
听我们这一曲
We may seem as different
你我天差地异
As the night is from day
像黑夜与晨曦
But you look a little deeper
但当抛开这些分歧
And you will see
你会发现
That I'm just like you
其实你像我
And you're just like me
而我像你
Yeah!
耶
Hey, hey, everybody
嘿，嘿，大家注意
We're here to shout
听我们唱
That the magic of friendship
用那歌声把友谊魔法四处传扬
Is what it's all about
Yeah, we thought we were different
你我天差地异
As the night is from the day
像那黑夜与晨曦
Until Twilight Sparkle
但是暮暮却将我们团结为一
Helped us see another way
So get up, get down
来飞扬，启航
If you're gonna come around
我们携手向远方
We can work together
一起帮助暮暮
Helping Twilight win the crown
把那桂冠戴头上
So get up, get down
来飞扬，启航
'Cause it's gonna make a sound
嘹亮歌声传四方
一起帮助暮光闪闪把那桂冠戴头上
If we work together
Helping Twilight Sparkle win the crown
Hey, hey, hands up now
嘿，嘿，手举高
We're sending a message to the crowd
让大家听见咱口号
Hands wave up, then come down
举过头，放至腰
We party together all around
派对时刻开始了
Generous, honesty
我慷慨，你诚信
Laughter, kindness, loyalty
欢笑，善良与忠心
Twilight helped us each to see
暮暮帮我们认清
All that we can be!
我们的本性
So get up, get down
来 飞扬， 启航
If you're gonna come around
我们携手向远方
We can work together
一起帮助暮暮
Helping Twilight win the crown
把那桂冠戴头上
So get up, get down
来飞扬，启航
'Cause it's gonna make a sound
嘹亮歌声传四方
If we work together
一起帮助暮光闪闪把那桂冠戴头上
Helping Twilight Sparkle win the crown
I'm gonna be myself
无论何时何地
No matter what I do
要坚持做自己
And if we're different, yeah
你我若有分歧
I want you to be true to you
就让心灵指引你
If you follow me
跟随我足迹
We'll put our differences aside
请放下我们的疑虑
We'll stick together and
让我们一起努力
Start working on that school pride!
只为学校争口气
Jump up, make a sound Hey!
起跳，齐声喊，嘿
Stomp your hooves, turn around
跺跺脚，转一转
Start now, make a change
现在就改变
Gonna come around
旧貌换新颜
Jump up, make a sound Hey!
起跳，齐声喊，嘿
Stomp your hooves, turn around
跺跺脚，转一转
Canterlot Wondercolts
坎特拉 奇骏团
Help her win the crown
请帮她夺冠
Jump up, make a sound Hey!
起跳，齐声喊，嘿
Stomp your hooves, turn around
跺跺脚，转一转
Start now, make a change
现在就改变
Gonna come around
旧貌换新颜
Jump up, make a sound Hey!
起跳，齐声喊，嘿
Stomp your hooves, turn around
跺跺脚，转一转
Canterlot Wondercolts
坎特拉 奇骏团
Help her win the crown
请帮她夺冠
Jump up, make a sound Hey!
起跳，齐声喊，嘿
Stomp your hooves, turn around
跺跺脚，转一转
Start now, make a change
现在就改变
Gonna come around
旧貌换新颜
Jump up, make a sound Hey!
起跳，齐声喊，嘿
Stomp your hooves, turn around
跺跺脚, 转一转
Take those off
给我摘下来